OK. I hope you can hear me clearly, right?
Or do you need me to move a little bit? Yes,
OK. OK, great. So, we are now
um in the 2nd week learning this cryptography,
and we're still in this quarter here.
So I hope you have watched my product recording for
RSA and DH uh algorithm, different Hellman.
So these two algorithms are the um basics
we, we discuss all these applications, right?
So, so, so only by knowing them, um, and then you probably can understand
better how this works. And now if you haven't watched them,
you just now imagine you know there there are some algorithms
which can help generating um one public key and a
private key pair. OK, so one public key and one private key.
So this key can be used in all this scenario now,
right? So the encryption key and decryption,
they must be different. Right. So we will focus on the
case study. And in those cases we discussed in last week,
which requires authenticity, non reputation,
and or sometimes integrated, integrate integrity together,
right? So we will discuss how this asymmetric crypto algorithm
can help in achieving those security goals,
OK? So then we will mainly talk about different
application scenario and see how we can use them and how we can combine different
algorithms. To guarantee they have different security goals
achieved, right? So what we were talking about.
Combining DS, triple, or AES and some hash
algorithm, and they can guarantee the confidentiality and
integrity together, right? So in your uh workshop,
I think you try to use some MD5 hash, right,
to create a signature so that you can check whether original
code was modified or not, right? So that integrated can be checked.
And then they can be combined together so that we can have the integrated and
confidentiality together. And today we'll talk about how do we use this
different algorithm. Combine them to guarantee
authenticity and non-repudiation, OK.
So, remember in a symmetric, while we have asymmetric,
we were discussing some scenario cases, right?
Uh, one is that e-commerce case, and millions of customers,
they need to communicate with the server.
Of course, the server doesn't want to generate a symmetric key
for each of his customers. And in that case,
the cus the server has to generate millions of key,
right, symmetric keys, which are different for each customer,
right, that's not scalable, right? And uh by using
symmetric, uh, which is why we need a symmetric.
And for online conferencing, the same thing.
If we want to keep each two. Party in that online
conferencing to be able to securely exchange messages.
And then we got to have N times N minus 1
divided by 2, that many keys to guarantee each two parties in this
online conferencing um scenario to be able to talk to each
other secretly, right? So, and also there's a
Issue for who will distribute these keys,
right, who will generate these keys, and who will oversee all the um
communication, right, um, key pair exchanging and
maybe expiry date and all that kind of stuff,
right? So there's no key distribution, so we want to
solve that issue as well. And then, and then also we want to
ensure the right party are communicating,
which means, how can we, how can we authenticate?
We're talking to the right right party. By,
by, by symmetric, there's no way uh we can
authenticate another party, right? So, we got to make sure,
remember, in symmetric, we just want to share a key with our receiver
and. And however, if we share the key to a wrong person,
and then the big issue will happen, right?
So the wrong person will be able to access to all the secret data you
want to share with him, right? So we've got to make sure the key can be shared to the
right right party. So we have to have
authenticity, OK. So then that's what a symmetric
can do. OK, can solve all these issues. And then you can see with
asymmetric and symmetric when we compare um the security
service provided by Each different type.
And of course, they both need to uh combine,
need to be combined with hash algorithm,
right? And with symmetric, we can at most guarantee these two features,
but with asymmetric, we can guarantee all these four features,
right? Availability is not a goal here. So we have,
we only have the other four goals can be achieved by either,
um, yeah, by this asymmetric, but symmetric can only achieve these two goals,
OK? So now here is the first scenario. And we
want to use SMS. Encryption and decryption
to achieve confidentiality. So, um, the
case here is, now let's imagine based on RSA
algorithm, OK, in my preductory coding. There is a key,
a public key and a private key pair generated for,
for all these people, right, so everyone can have his own
private key and public key pair. Right, so a key pair is
generated for Alice and key pair is generated for Bob.
And then if we now want to uh have the key
exchanging, right? So, Alice wants to get Bob's public key,
and Bob will share that public key. Right?
And what happens here is, if we, we can imagine that Bob,
that Bob is Amazon and Alice is customer here.
So, customer wants to get Bob's Amazon's public uh
public key. And then later, this customer can encrypt his
credit card information by using Amazon's public key.
OK, so, um, the customer wants to buy
something from Amazon. Of course, most of the service online,
right? So the customer is encrypting his own credit card information by using
a third party, for example, PayPal, Alipay,
right, by those online payment companies,
um, publicly, but We just, uh, by simplify this
procedure, we just assume the customer can directly talk to Amazon.
Amazon can directly charge this customer's credit card,
and then, and then Amazon is the only one who can see this
customer's credit card information, OK. Um,
Yeah So let's assume that's the case here,
right? So the customer is talking to has got Amazon's
public key and customer can use Amazon's public key to do an
encryption. So now I just uh pay attention to this color.
I use a different color. It's orange color and then belongs
to Bob, OK? Amazon site. So what Amazon,
what Alice, the customer would do here is to To an
encryption by using
Amazon's public key, and then The Amazon will
use this Amazon's private key to do a decryption so
that Amazon can read that credit card information and charge credit card,
right? So encryption and decryption must be a different key,
right? Must be different. So now you can also imagine you all in this
room are the customer um um of Amazon.
And you all want to buy something from Amazon.
And by assuming you all know Amazon's public key,
right? And then You can then encrypt your credit card information
by Amazon's public key and you send to Amazon,
right? If anyone else in the room also get that message,
you got this encrypted message by using Amazon's public key and you also know
Amazon's public key, right? If you wish to use Amazon's public key to do a
decryption, that's, there's no way. So, So because that
RS algorithm guarantees only the associated
private key can be used for decryption. So if we know
Amazon's private key, of course we can do a decryption.
We can all read this customer's credit card information.
However, Amazon's private key is only kept by Amazon,
OK, by himself. So Amazon is the only one who can read your
credit card information. So this is how the confidentiality can be
kept, OK, achieved in this procedure.
Um, OK, so I just want to stop a little bit here.
I saw Joyce's, Joyce's question. Um, it the,
um, symmetric encryption can only guarantee confidentiality as it's a
separate hash that guarantees integrity.
And this new slide is that can guarantee and integrate.
So, um, sorry, yeah, there was a bit confusing here.
I added integrity and also added integrity here,
which all have to, um, this algorithm has to combine with
the Hash algorithm to guarantee both OK by
itself it only has in confidentiality. You're right.
And again for the asymmetric integrity was added here is because we
also consider the case we will, um, combine asymmetric and
hash. OK, when we combine the hash together here so the symmetric
can guarantee this both and the asymmetric and guarantee integrated here as well.
So we got to borrow the hash, OK. Um, in both
cases. OK. So,
now, um, you, you'll see how hash can be embedded and so that
these different features can be guaranteed.
OK, so here is how, how the customer is using
that. Orange, uh, belong to this Amazon
to do an encryption. And then the encrypted credit card
information, when Amazon received that one,
Amazon will use his own orange private key to
do a decryption and then he can read that text.
So that encrypted text, although it's shared online,
And if we don't have Amazon's private key,
which was kept by her, by himself, and then there's no way to
decrypt this encrypted text. So this is why we would say
the public key was used for encryption and the private key was used.
In decryption, and confidentiality can be kept,
OK? Confidentiality. So public key plus private key equals to
confidentiality. However, in my next slide,
remember the order of this public and private key,
which would be different when we want to keep the authenticity,
the private key and the public key. So private key is in the
1st place and public key was in the 2nd place,
which means we would use private key for encryption and the public key
for decryption. And then that can help to guarantee
authenticity. OK, so, Um,
again, there's a key exchanging system, but in this case,
we would imagine the customer is Bob and Alice is Amazon in this
site. You can now imagine, we want, a customer want to guarantee the
message is truly from Amazon. So how Amazon can prove
his own message is actually uh from Amazon,
not from someone else. So we want to have authenticity here in
this application. So what Amazon has to do
is to encrypt a message he wants to share
by using his own private key, OK, which is this
blue key. OK. So he will encrypt by using
that blue, his own private key, and then he will share with
this customer. And after this customer receives that message,
because the customer has access to Amazon's public key,
and then the customer can use Amazon's public key to do a decryption.
When the customer can read the message and decrypt the message by using
this. Amazon's public key and this customer has the
confidence that message he received was actually from Amazon.
So this is how private key for encryption,
public key for decryption is to be used in keeping this
authenticity. Right. So this is what,
what, um, happens here. So,
Amazon's private key was used for encryption,
and Amazon, before sending that message,
he will firstly encrypt his own message by using his private key.
And then when customer receive, the customer will use Amazon's public key
to do a decryption. When This customer saw that
message can be decreed by using Amazon's publicly,
so this customer knew. The original tax must have
been increased by using Amazon's private key,
which is only known by Amazon himself, not by anyone
else. OK. Of course, this has assumed this customer has the right
public key belonging to Amazon at the very first step.
Now, sorry, let, let's imagine, um, maybe I,
I, I know probably some, some of you would be confused in this case,
right? So we are using the private key for encryption and public key for decryption,
OK, in this uh keeping authenticity case.
And let's now imagine in this classroom,
virtual classroom, OK, now here we have 28 people in
total, right? And then Remember, the public key is
meant to be public, OK? And we can share them without any
worry, right? So, the 28 people in this room
can generate 28 key pair, OK. Each of us has the
ability to run our essay algorithm, and we can all generate a public
key and a private key which belongs to ourselves.
OK, so there will be 28 key pairs belonging to different people.
Of course, in each of these key pair that public key must be different from other
people's public key, and private key pair private key is also different from other people.
OK. So, now. Let's assume we
all share our public key to other 27 people in this room.
Then that means we all have a list, OK? We,
we all have a list of 27 public key in our list,
OK, I have. The 27 um public key
belong to Joy, uh, belong to Asa, belong to all
you here and Michael and yeah, Russfall.
So we, we, we, I have all that public key at least,
OK, belong to all different people. So because at the very beginning,
we just share all that information. And we trust each other and
we trust that the public key shared by Joe is actually Joy's public key and I put
that one on my list. And I also trust all other people,
so I have that clean public key list, OK,
in my paper. So now I want to um
OK, remember you also have the other 27 people's public key and you put on
your paper, right? So now, I want to share
an important message. OK. That important message is,
OK, exam question are in these links, and you need to
submit by what date, OK, so I put that message.
To this room. However, when you receive that message,
you can see that plain text and you will doubt whether that
link is a good link or not, right? So you can't trust.
This message is actually from Hui, right?
So although that I put my name, I said I can't regards Hui in
attached to that message, but you probably won't believe,
right? So you, you think that plain text is forgeable very easily,
right. So what I will do is I will add
my authenticity to this message. So what I will
do is I will encrypt by using
my private key, OK, my here, right. So remember,
encrypt by using public private key. So I encrypt my
exam announcement message by using my private key.
And then I will send to you, right? So
after you receive that message, which is encrypted text,
and you will check the list because you,
you saw that message, um, claimed to be sent by Hui.
So you check Hui's public key from your list.
And then You will use Hu's publicly to do a
decryption. Now here in this after decryption,
you saw that message which has a link for all exam questions and
you trust that message was actually from Hui because you can,
you are able to use Hui's public key to do a
decryption, right? So then you trust. Hui has
initially put her own private key attached to the message
or encrypted to the encrypted on the message and then that's why you can use Hui's
public key to do a decryption so you believe that
original text which was encrypted by Hui's private
key and which can only be decrypted
by his public key, not by. Robert's public
key or Aus's public key or another person's public key,
right? So you believe that text was
attached with Identity which belongs to
Hui herself. My private key is kind of identity in this
case, right? So I have signed my message by using
my own private key. Private key meant to be a private key,
which I don't share with anyone else. The same.
thing as your own private key. If you want to share a
private message to someone else, you want to add your authenticity to that
message, what you can do is the same thing.
You encrypt your message by your own private key,
and then you share with another. People,
right. Other people, when they got this message,
they want to verify whether that message was actually from you or
from Hu, from Robert, and they would pick up your public key from the
list and then they will use that public key to do a decryption.
And then that's the um the case how we can
add authenticity to our own message, right?
So, so that's the, the case here, OK. So
that's why also that's why we call that a signature text because that text has
been signed by or has been encrypted by this Alice private key.
And another person can use that associated public key to
verify that. The message was actually from Alice or from
Hui, right, because Hui is the only one who has her own private key.
That's how we can verify how we can authenticate that person or that message was
actually from Hui or from another person.
OK. So This is the
of course in this scenario we have assumed
we all have a clean list, clean list, OK,
of other people's public key. We all know,
um, that public keys actually belong to Hui and that probably actually belong to Robert
and there's no, uh, fake public key shared at the very first
step, right? And also for my other slides,
this, this place here. Um, here, right? So when a
customer wants to encrypt his, uh, credit card information,
this customer has made sure he's using Amazon's public key
to do an encryption, and then Amazon can decrypt his credit card information because
Amazon is the only one who has that private key,
right? So we assume that public key in the first place is the true.
Um, public key belong to Amazon, not to forge the key by some,
uh, I mean, there's a way to share the public key at the very first step.
The public key actually belongs to someone,
but of course there's a case the public key can be breached or can be replaced by a
hacker, right? So of course we've got to find a way later
to check how we can make sure the public key exchanging at the very first step.
Can be guaranteed and can be a um a step which has
no problem, OK. So, So we have that
authenticity and why this is why we use a private key
plus public key equals to authenticity, but we can also use a public key
plus private key to guarantee the confidentiality.
So RSA can RSA can guarantee this confidentiality
authenticity, OK, by using this RSA algorithm.
OK. Um, so we have, we have, based on this RSA
algorithm, we can also have the other, um,
scenario. So before I talk about my next scenario,
I want to answer Robert's question. Robert says,
if both Amazon and the customer exchange the encrypted
message, both Amazon and the customer need a public and a private key that needs
to be generated and shared. Why is this largely easier than sharing
symmetric keys? OK, so remember the private
key not to be shared with anyone, right?
Public key is public. OK. The public key,
uh, you don't have to keep it secretly. We just announced that one,
OK, through the air. So Amazon can announce his public key
is something, and now you can imagine all customers,
millions of customers all get that public key,
OK? The millions of customers all get that public key and all this customers in this room
can get that public key. And the private key though is kept by Amazon
to, to himself. He doesn't share with any other people.
And then when we as a customer, you remember there are millions of
customers. We want to buy things from Amazon.
What we will do is we will all use the single public key,
OK. Issued by Amazon. And we all
encrypt our credit card information by using that only public
key shared by Amazon, right? And then we
encrypt our credit card information and send it to the air.
And then when another hacker can also get that encrypted credit card
information, but another hacker, if he doesn't have that private key,
which belongs to Amazon, he's not able to decrypt
the credit card information. And only Amazon,
who has that private key, which kept by her by himself,
he can use that private key to do a decryption on those encrypted
texts. So, Amazon would be the only one who can read our
credit card information. So in this scenario,
instead of keeping or generating millions of symmetric keys
to be shared with millions of these customers,
right, those symmetric keys must be different,
remember, right? So only be different than this
Amazon can do a secured decryption.
However, this Amazon now has only one key pair,
which is public key and private key pair.
Public public key is shared by, OK, with millions of
customers. And the private key is kept by Amazon himself,
right? So by using that one key pair here.
Each customer can encrypt his own credit card information
very safely and shared with Amazon. And Amazon
is the only one who can Decrypt that credit card information.
Charge your credit card, and then that's it.
So the online purchase can be finished in this way,
right? So there's only one key pair needed in this case,
OK. So which is different from this symmetric key,
but in symmetric case, right, symmetric key case.
Amazon has to generate millions of different symmetric keys for
millions of customers. And each customer has his own symmetric key and
encrypt his credit card information, shared with Amazon.
And Amazon has to use that exact same key.
Kept for this customer to decrypt his credit card information and for different customers he
has to find a different key, right, to do a decryption.
However, in this public and private key usage application.
Amazon only needs to generate one key. One public key and one
private key, right? And he can get charged for all
his customers, right, all his customers will just use that public key
to do an encryption and public key is not to be,
uh, securely shared. It can be announced in the air and everyone can access to
that public key. Right, so this is a much,
much more efficient and no one needs to do a key
distribution, distribution, and no one needs to generate millions of key pairs,
right? So only Amazon needs to share that only key pair,
OK. Um Yeah, and Raffle
um said there will be a certificate from CA,
which is of course my question there. We assumed that Amazon can
share his public key with all his customers very securely,
but how, right? How can we make sure a customer is
is encrypting his credit card information by using Amazon public key,
not an attacker's public key, right? And then this customer thought
the attacker's public key belong belonged to Amazon.
So how can we make sure that public key at the very first place is a
legitimate public key? We've got to have a way to prove that one.
So now let's just assume there's a way to share the public key safely
and then to um have. Some proof that public key
actually belongs to Amazon, actually belongs to Hu,
actually belongs to everyone in this virtual room.
So let's assume that public key share when we share and then that public key can be
trusted, trustable, right. OK.
Yeah, so, um, so Robert, and
you have more questions about different ones for each kind that needs to be generated for data
from Amazon to the customer. Of course we are talking about different scenario
here, right? So when we talk about to keep confidentiality and we only have
the case where um Each customer wants to include
their own credit card and share with Amazon.
So in that case, one key pair generated by Amazon is enough.
But in another scenario, if we all want to authenticate ourselves,
We, of course, we, each one in this room will generate a key pair
and we want to add our identity, OK, in this digital space,
and we all want to authenticate. But again,
the public key is not to be shared securely,
but in symmetric encryption, you need to guarantee the symmetric
key is shared securely. But in public and
private key case, The public key can be shared in the air
without any encryption. OK, public key is public key.
We just Put them out and then that you don't have
to worry about how public key because public is meant to be public.
We're not saying, oh, the symmetric key,
you've got to find a way to very safely share the
symmetric key between the sender and receiver,
right? Remember, right, we've got to make sure that symmetric key can only be known by those two
parties, but for public key. We don't care.
The public key is public, OK, we just share them,
right, no problem. So that's another difference here,
OK. OK, so now let's come back to this
document signing case study. So if there's a case where
Alice wants to sign some message and then send to Bob
a secret message, right, so Alice doesn't want to
Avis would be able to change that message to like
Alice owns Avis. $10 or Alice also wants,
doesn't want. Bob can claim, OK, you don't owe me $10 you owe me
$1000 right? So when Alice sends that message,
Alice wants to make sure her message won't be modified
by anyone, right? He, she also wants to,
uh, let Bob believes the message was actually from Alice.
Alice has put a signature to her message.
So when Bob received it. Bob has the confidence that Alice sent that
message and that's a true message was not that message was not modified
by anyone in the middle, right? So, Alice wants to
get some signature to put on on her message,
right? So, Alice wants to make sure that signature is authentic,
unalterable, not reusable, not
repudiated, right? So, The solution here
is What Alice could do is he
Uh, she will use a hash function to create
a signature, OK, or with a fingerprint here,
right, to To generate hash and in your workshop you
have used the like MD5 sum right just one simple command or
to create a different type of hash you just change your command you can generate hash,
right. So this is a hash to original uh
message and then with this message with this hash.
Alice wants to put her own authenticity to her message.
So Alice will use her own private key to do
encryption on this fingerprint. And
then this is an encrypted fingerprint. You can't see any
message inside, right? So because it has been encrypted by using Alice's
private key. So in the receiver end,
Receiver received this plain text from um shared
by Alice maybe by email or by text. OK, so by another channel and
then Bob received this message. Bob wants to verify whether that message is a
true one or or a wrong one, right? Or maybe Alice sent
by email and send this message and attach such a
Um, hashed, OK, result to that message, OK,
and sent together to Bob, right? Bob received this one and also this one.
And now Bob wants to verify whether this message is a true message or not.
So Bob will generate a signature, OK, um,
by using a shot one function. And then Bob will
also because there's a a red block received.
So Bob knew that message was included by using
Alice's private key. So because public key Bob has received,
so Bob will use Alice's public key to do a decryption.
So after using this Alice public key to do a decryption,
Alice got, I'm sorry, Bob got this one, this signature.
And then Bob will check the hash signature of original message
and this and this decrypted message. When these two messages
are exactly the same, so Bob knew there's no
modification on that message here, and this
message. Has been encrypted by using Alice private key,
and Alice is the only one who can access that private key.
So Bob knew that message has already been
added that authenticity, right? Or sometimes we say
that message has been attached Alice's
identity because the private key here represents
Alice's identity. In our virtual space, right?
So We, because we are able to use Alice public key to do a
decryption which means original message must have been encrypted by
using Alice private key, so which is why we can
believe this message Bob receives is a
true message which was, um, which, which,
um, has embedded. With Alice's
private key or identity, OK. Authenticity is there and also a
signature has been added, like, sorry, don't use signature here,
fingerprint here, and the hash, um, result here
proves that integrity of that message, right?
And also in this message by receiving that one,
OK, by Bob and Bob. Has the confidence that no
repudiation has already has also been achieved right because
Alice can't deny later she doesn't own Bob $10
because Alice has sent that encrypted red box here.
Which proves Alice has already encrypted.
Only Alice can encrypt it by using Alice's private key.
No one else can, right? So non-reputation has also been achieved here.
So non-reputation, integrity, and also authenticity
has all been achieved, right, which makes that signature,
um, authentic, unalterable. Not
reusable, cannot be repudiated. Right, so
Alice has used this way to encrypt her message,
OK, and then sent to Bob. So everything here has been,
um, guaranteed. Now let's imagine, um, the same thing
happened from Alice's side, but Alice, uh,
but in Bob's side for some reason, and there's a message which
is like this, and now you can imagine when you generate a hash.
This hash will be different from this decrypted hash,
right? So decrypted hash would be a different one.
And then when Bob saw different message,
different hash, and Bob knew this message was not true,
OK, so there's no integrity there. This is how Bob knew.
And then you can also see in those, um, code
signing scenario. Um, when we want to make sure the code is authentic,
actually sourced by the publisher, and has not been modified since it left the
software's publisher, and the publisher cannot deny they published the code,
and what they can do is with the code, they can also do the same thing.
They add such a small red block, OK. And which also was
encrypted by using the publisher's private key so the publisher can't deny
later, right? The publisher has proved the integrity and also authenticity
of their themselves, right? And another case which was
used very similar is the digital certificate.
Which is You can imagine there's a Cisco or another university,
right, and then they want to issue a digital certificate if they're a student
when a student graduates. So what they would do is they will firstly,
Ask for your date of birth, your name, right,
your graduation year, and then they will generate a hash based on all that information.
So this hash will then be encrypted by using
Cisco's private key. If Cisco wants to add his own.
Um, authenticity there, right, because Cisco needs to prove he actually
issued that certificate. So Cisco will then encrypt that whole
hash by using Cisco's private key. And then they generate
number. That number is a unique digital number
attached to your certificate, right? And then so that number will
be stored um or attached to your digital certificate and also stored
in the cloud or database somewhere, right?
And then remember that number. And then when you uh
later get a job and then your HR officer,
they will have to verify your digital certificate is it true or not,
right? So, Then in that case, the HR
officer will use the system and to check,
to verify. So what that system is doing is,
you will again, um, the system will ask you to provide your graduation year,
your name, your ID information. Um, date of birth,
all that kind of information, they will confirm that order and then they will generate hash,
OK, so which is this hash at the same time because you provided
them your digital certificate, right, so which is the number.
Attached to a digital certificate, right?
So then they know that number was certified by Cisco.
So they will use Cisco's public key to verify,
to do a decryption. Then when they decrypt that
number and they can see this number and then
they will verify these two numbers if they are the same and then they
knew you actually got that certificate from Cisco.
OK, that's a true certificate provided by you.
Otherwise if they got a different reason,
different results here, so they knew. Uh,
either probably you accidentally provide the wrong information here or
your digital signature is not correct. OK,
you're here, right, your digital certificate is a fake one,
right? So this is how, how the digital certificate was
generated based on the similar like technique,
right. And then the digital certificate can be authentic.
OK, authenticity, integrity, non-repudiation are all embedded to
this digital certificate. OK, so now to talk
about the last scenario, right, right, OK,
based on public and private key. Remember,
in all above scenario I've discussed, we have assumed
that public key is a true public key, right?
So actually belong to Cisco. There's a way to access
to a public key which actually belongs to Cisco.
And remember when we as a customer using Amazon's public key to do an encryption
on our credit card, also assumed. We have
access to the right Amazon's public key,
right? What if The public key
is not actually belong to Amazon. So you can imagine in this
case, Alice here is the Amazon site, right?
Bob um wants to encrypt his credit card by
using Amazon's public key, which should be this green key,
right? So Bob should use this green key to do an
encryption on his own credit card. However,
for some reason, Avis Is the man in the middle,
OK, so he launched this man in the middle attack.
He replaced his red key. OK, to that
green key. So that green key was replaced with this red key.
And however, Bob doesn't know. Bob thought that red key
is Amazon's public key, so Bob used red key to do an
encryption on his own credit card information and then who can read
that credit card? Is it Amazon, Alice, or is it Evis?
It must be AIS, right, because the credit card was encrypted by
using AIs public key. So only Avis now can read that credit
card information, right? So how can we ensure
at the very first step we get Amazon's public
key, which is a true Amazon's public key rather than someone else,
right? How can Amazon By um, like a provider,
OK, this online shop private provider. How can he
guarantee his public key is not forged by a man in the
middle attacker and to replace his own public key to
someone else, with someone else. Yes,
certificate, right? So this is one certificate.
Like, um, Which actually certified
by global sign organization, OK, and which
proved some public key belongs to Amazon or belongs
to another company. If you go to your browser,
you actually can see. OK, in your network setting,
and this is my Chrome, right. So in your network setting,
uh, and security place and you can check your own.
And you can see a lot of certificate was um
stored by my Chrome browser. So this is what my
Chrome browser would do for me. So he will actually check whether Amazon's
public key is a legitimate public key or not.
If it's the right one, certified by another per another
big company or a global association. And then this
browser will trust this customer is actually visiting the legitimate
Amazon and providing his credit card information to the right party rather than a fake
party, right? So these are all means some
certificate of authority which certified that public key
actually belongs to someone. Right? So when a small business
start a small business, right? So when you provide a website,
what this small business also has to do is to
probably pay some money to a big company or to some
countries, um, association or organization,
uh, who can certify. A public key actually belongs to them,
right? So this is service this big company can
provide which is called certificate signing request.
So what does it mean? It will, it actually means they will
certify Amazon's public key is something and they will
add a hash and they will also sign by um certificate authority's
private key. So which means the certificate of authority,
you cannot imagine it's just the one company here it's a big reputable security company
Semantic. OK, so he has one public key and a private key
pair, right, this big company and that public key has been
certified by a government, right, so known by everyone,
right. So and then private key pair associated with that public key,
OK, belongs to this semantic and now. This big
company certifies that Amazon's public key is this,
and also a hash was generated and then encrypted.
The whole message was encrypted by the semantics private key.
So that's a certificate. A given to Amazon.
Right, so when you, you are visiting Amazon website,
what your browser is doing behind the thing is
your browser will seek semantics public key
to do a decryption and then to
sorry put here. OK, your, your, uh,
browser would do because that has been signed by semantics private key,
right? So the whole message, the certificate,
your browser will use semantics public key to do a decryption
and then get this clear message. So he got the decrypted
message hash and he also can see that public key here.
The public key he will do, he will generate.
Uh hash. And then he will compare these two
hash, right. So if these two hashs are the same,
then your browser would believe, OK, that public key is the right one.
Otherwise he wouldn't trust that public key,
right? So this is how Amazon has requested some big
company to sign on his own public key to give some proof.
On that public key is something, right, and then Because we
have all these different certificate authority to prove a
public key is actually true, and then this browser
or another party can believe that public key is the true one,
right? Otherwise, we wouldn't have that confidence that public key is
actually belongs to Amazon and then so that's the um
That's the, the way, OK, what certificate authority is doing.
So he's actually providing that service to a
lot of small companies when they want to start a website and
then when sometimes when your browser visits somewhere and then your browser
would remind you or send out a warning that this certificate is
not proved by a big company, which actually means.
Their public key was not a re recognizable uh one and
also not proved by another certificate authority,
right? So that's why you will get some warning at that time.
And um because that small business hasn't asked for this request to,
to provide that confidence to the market.
And then because they didn't pay or sometimes this also needs to be
periodically issued with that certificate,
and it has an expiry date. Right, so this is um
about how do we prove that public key is true and so that the customer can use the right public
key to, to send that encrypted message to,
to the, um, Uh, right party. OK, so of
course there are more cryptography algorithms,
um, more or less, um, they're quite, uh,
yeah, the, their purpose are all achieving,
um, These 5 goals, but of course, not availability,
but all other 4 goals and combining with different,
and they have different properties, um, maybe a speed wise or
basic operation wise, but now we, we only focus on seman semantics.
I'm sorry, symmetric last time and then this time we talk about asymmetric.
Now you understand all this um scenario,
we actually will discuss um how to use this asymmetric in our
workshop and then you can also see how asymmetric can help
um in keeping these different security goals,
right. OK. So there are a lot of applications
and in week 5, next week, we'll talk about authentication,
which again based on this public and private key,
asymmetric um infrastructure. And then week
78, we will talk about that SSL um secure
layer. Protocol, uh, what are the, um,
how this symmetric and asymmetric are combined,
right, to guarantee, um, different security goals
in these protocols. OK. So that's all for today.
I hope if you haven't watched, um, the pre-lecture recording,
please do make sure you watch them before your workshop,
uh, and then otherwise, yeah, you probably feel you.
Feel confused sometimes, OK? So we only focus
on application in this week. I hope you understand
them well, and if not, let's discuss more about teams.
OK? Thank you, everyone. That's all for today.